■ Overview:
  ---------
This GPS Device driver is a software component that provides an interface through Data control of DMA over UART
The GPS interface offers control function over GPS, To Request GPS from UART over DMA and to parse the GPS Data
to get the required sentence which is GPRMC data format.

■  Technical features and user guide:
  -----------------------------------
■  Description
  -------------
The GPS Driver Provides 2 Functionalities:
* Get the GPS DATA; by requesting a receiption transfer from UART over DMA
* Parse the received data To get the required sentence from the total GPS data. 	

The above functionalitites are acheived using 3 states:
* GPS_READY
* GPS_DONE_RECEIVEING
* GPS_DONE_PARSING

The Driver provides 4 functions 
-----------------------------------
1- GPS_Init(): This function provides initialization to the global Variables and initiating the First state
   which is GPS_READY.

2- GPS_ReqData(uint8_t UART_ID): This function generates a request from the GPS driver to be sent over UART to Get the next
   Packet of data (1024) Byte.

   This function is Asynchronous which means it is excuted on 2 states, The first one is to check if the GPS
   is Ready it initiates the request on UART.

   Once the Data is available, DMA generate an interrupt over UART to indicate the transmission is done.
   On that Interrupt, The third function is called

3- GPS_ReceptionDone(): This function is a callback function which is called when the GPS has received its 
   Data packet. It changes the state To be GPS_Done_Receiving.

   On the Next call of GPS_ReqData(), it detects that the current state is GPS_DONE_RECEIVING, So it calls 
   the last function which is GPS_GetData()

4- GPS_GetData(uint8_t InputArray[],uint8_t GPRMCData[]): This Function Takes the 1024 packet of Data and extracts
   the Valid  GPRMC Sentence Out of it putting it on GPRMCData array.


■  Steps
   -----
   Call GPS_ReqData(uint8t_t UART_ID) 2 Times to Receive the Required GPRMC Data on the global array GPRMCData.
   
